This one?
Yeah.
You, me, you and everyone else.
Who bought it?
Did you buy it?
A-ra?
Did Aiara buy it?
Yeah.
Yuko bought one too?
Did you buy it, Mr. Tasaki?
No, no, I bought it for Ms. Tasaki.
Oh, I heard. I heard.
That's great!
Yeah, I heard.
I heard.
Thank you.
Lazily.
Always.
I don't know, I'm already nervous.
Oh, for heaven's sake.
It's from Swister.
Swister to you, sir.
It's from Mr. Swister.
Are you free later tonight?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's make it eight weeks.
That's what it's like to be somewhere else today.
Applause.
Are you free later tonight?
Would you like to go out with me?
I've always wanted to talk with Shunsuke Setoguchi.
Even after the rain stopped, the party was still going on.
Se-no, amerge mo ame flash ame lee.
Ame shabe for short.
Combined with Yuzuki's room.
Jamaimo's Yuzuki's Room Special.
Good evening to all of you who are watching the official YouTube Live Ameflash channel.
Good evening.
Good evening. We are AmeFlash.
Please come on in.
So, each and every time...
Where we say 00 and...
hashtag
from those who have tweeted us candyflash tweets.
I'm going to call them by name today.
Today, I have chosen Mr. Setoguchi, who has been advertising that there will be a "candy chat".
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Setoguchi-san.
He wrote that he is going to appear on the program.
Thank you very much.
Please look forward to it.
And here comes the spacha.
Ahikazuman-san has sent us a Yuzuki's Room collaboration commemorative.
Thank you very much.
Yes, so tonight's Abishab will be from a different place than usual.
We are broadcasting from the studio of Yuzuki Yuzuki's Room, the show of Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Shachi.
I never thought I would be able to do it here.
We are borrowing a part of the studio.
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's really not that important.
What is it?
Oh!
Ooh!
Oh, but it's a nice change of heart.
So it's not important.
It's the same thing.
Um, please continue.
Once again, let me explain Yuzuki's Room,
Yuzuki's Room is a program that is broadcasted on Team Shirt's official YouTube channel every Monday night at 9:00 p.m.
Yes, everyone.
Everyone is here.
How was it being a guest on the show?
The whole time, there was some kind of inaudible voice and it was bad the whole time.
The air conditioner was connected all the time.
So when I started to fly backstage separately.
Are you okay? Were you in some kind of meeting or something?
It was backstage.
Yes, okay.
I understand.
Okay.
Yes, thank you very much.
We are all guests.
Come on, let's all go a few more times,
Yes.
I'm really happy to be here.
And we here at Ameflatation, we have a live program called Amebabble every Monday night at 8:00 p.m., so we'll have a little bit of Amebabble until 9:00 p.m. and then we'll go on.
So we have a little bit of Ameba-Speak until 9:00 p.m., and then we go on to the next room.
I guess it's the usual course of the show,
I'm like, "Oh, yeah, I'm going to go to my room.
I guess that's the usual course, right?
That's right. But, you know,
It's supposed to be a nice flow.
It's a good time of the day, right?
But, you know, because of Kojima Hana, who has the MC title at Ameshabu.
Because of Hana Kojima,
And she's off today due to a scheduling conflict,Moreover, he said he was closed today due to a scheduling conflict,
Huh?
Because of Kojimahana's bad manners,
Yeah, I know.
It's a bit of a reality that we always end up about 20 minutes late every time.
It's a bit of a reality, isn't it?
That's right.
I always end up pushing.
Even though I'm covering for my senior's show,
I'm sorry, but I'm going to be on the show,
Thank you very much.
I really appreciate that our Mr. Kojima shows his own dog videos even though he is pushing for more and more.
He is so stubborn that he will always do his own corner.
That's right.
Today, I'm covering my backside a little bit, because I didn't see any reporters coming.
So God was watching.
That's right. He was watching.
I think He was watching.
He was watching us.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
But you know, when Yuzuki's room starts, the number of views on Ameshame always goes down.
Yuzuki-chan might not be damaged by that.
I see.
How did you get on Yuzuki's room on such short notice?
Maybe you should explain it to her.
You're not the oldest, are you?
Look at me and tell me.
You're the oldest, but you're leaving all the fuss to the younger ones?
You want to talk a lot, don't you?
Sorry, sorry.
If I have to explain to you later, I won't say anything about the candy.
Explain.
Go, go, go!
What's with you older guys?
Let me explain. Yuzuki and I collaborated on a song together.
We collaborated on a song for our candy flossies, and at the end we had a talk together.
Yuzuki-chan said, "The room festival was great, but next time, I'd like to see Yuzuki-chan on YouTube.
Yuzuki-chan told us that the Room Fest was great, but that she would be happy if we could appear in Yuzuki's room on YouTube next time.
We've been wanting to do it for a long time, too.
We'll be on soon! We'll be on tomorrow if you want! We said something like that.
Then the day after tomorrow? So we said, "Well, maybe the day after tomorrow.
He was more light-hearted.
Then the day after tomorrow.
The staff didn't say anything about it.
We haven't been told it's okay either.
Then we'll put it out the day after tomorrow.
We'll do it on our own.
I'll take the liberty of saying that.
I've just said that
This time it was OK.
If we can do it that way, it will be our home concert.
It's great, isn't it?
I didn't think we'd be able to do it.
You know. We are so glad that you came on such short notice.
I'm really glad you had a drink with us.
Thank you.
The theme is respect.
Yes, that's right.
Well, we are a group of one staff member.
So you are open to more urgent offers there.
That's right.
Momokuro-chan and the Devil in the House will stop their crushes, etc,
We are always here.
Yes, we are always here.
We are looking forward to hearing from you.
We are waiting for you.
No, we're not waiting for you.
This is Yusake's studio.
You're intruding on your senior's show,
And you're calling for offers from other programs.
What?
That's absolutely wrong. It's rude.
You guys have "rude" written all over your faces.
I can't push an idol with a rude face.
Yeah, you two rude faces are the reason I'm done.
It's always you guys who make a mess, you know.
You stupid idiots.
This is you.
But it says "cute" on your face, Mojikun.
Cute.
No, of course not.
Because he's cute.
Because everyone thinks you're cute.
No, that's as expected.
Well, take a look.
You're right.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Honjaya ya da!
You must be the staff of Yuzuki's Air. I can hear you.
It's zipping by. Someone is cutting out. They're starting to cut out.
I'm here for my senior's show, and I'm going to do the usual farce here.
One more time, I'm in a bit of trouble.
I'm getting scared, so I'm going to stop doing this show now.
I don't know what to do.
Did I talk about the rain?
I might say, "I talked about the rain.I might end up talking in the rain.
Well, you know, there are people who want to do this kind of thing, and Yuzukichan, too.
Six hundred people are watching us.
Thank you very much, Yuzuki.
Thank you very much.
Yuzuki-chan and Ms. Suzuguchi will also make a guest appearance on "Ameshabe" tonight.
I don't know when they will appear, so please don't miss the Yuzuki's Room without Ameshabe.
Please don't miss Yuzuki's room.
I will read the spacha before moving on to the next stage.
Mr. YTXZ Tail's Feelings
Oh, what?
Wait a minute.
What?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm always impressed by the Yuzuki and Ameba rooms. Great!
Listen!
Thank you.
Great timing on the scripts and all that.
Not too much!
It's got circles for emphasis.
It says when to brace.
It doesn't say when to brace.
It cuts off here like it's going to be here for a night.
No!
You're right.
You're a second generation actress.
I hope you're good at that.
That's exactly what I mean.
So that you can cut it.
I thought it was a voice training kashikara.
I thought it was just a kashkara, too.
There are others here, too.
Nao-san, congratulations on 300,000 views of Browiamind!
Thank you very much.
That's amazing.
Even though I didn't sing.
Hey, I'm really happy.
Ratman, thank you for your hard work at Yuzuki's Room festival rally.
Thank you very much.
Yes, for the episode about the Yuzuki's Room festival,
I would like to talk a lot about it in the main part of Yuzuki's Room after this,
Please look forward to it.
Now, let's talk about yesterday's release.
Shall we talk about this?
Yes, I do. It was the first time for Ambu Flash.
But it's been a long time since we've had Laraport, Tatehiko Tachikawa, right?
Yes, it has.
I wonder how many years it has been.
But I saw a tweet from a fan,
I looked at it and it says September 2017.
Five years ago?
Maybe a little bit five years ago.
That's terrible.
So, it's really around the end of 3WE, isn't it?
The first time?
Five years ago, so the last.
So we've been together for about 10 years now.
We did a lot of cover guests and stuff.
You were originally together with a large group called 3WE Junior, right?
If it was a large group, then there were more 3WE groups within that group.
You also had a smaller group.
This smaller group.
You know, like, "Here's a cover kick that you can dance to.
Ultrafest.
I mean, wasn't that something that was going to happen?
It was the day of the music station's Ultrafest.
The music station had been broadcasting live all morning for hours.
That's right!
I was playing three roles.
So that's Sora and Harry Mann.
Oh, that's Morilyn!
No, that's not it.
Morilyn probably played something with Ira.
Oh, that's Tetsuko Kuroyanagi. She did that.
That's another time.
Different time.
After that.
Then Solo did it in the spring.
I put on Katsuta and let the rain do the work.
That's right.
Tamori did it.
That was a long time ago.
It was like a long time ago when I came.
The way he looked at us from upstairs.
It was a long time ago.
But there were more people than usual.
I heard we had the largest crowd.
The menstrual dogs pay more than usual.
You heard voices like I gave it to you.
Some people didn't take their period and would watch them outside,
Some people would go out of their way to look at it, and so on,
There were also many people who came to the event like on TikTok,
I was so happy.
The influence of TikTok is amazing, isn't it?
I think we had the largest number of relatives.
Yes, there were a lot of relatives who lined up for the benefit event this Tachikawa Tachibana Day.
There were a lot of them.
It was as if all the people in the line for our usual benefit event were relatives.
I, or rather, Ayura's relatives were twice as many as my usual scoring rate.I, or rather, Ayura's relatives' praise was double my usual scoring rate.
What?
It was pretty amazing.
That's amazing.
It was really good.
I don't know, it was as if these people were going to be dispersed to all of us,
We were all so surprised to see them.
What a long time! I was so surprised to see them.
It's already turned around.
I was so surprised.
I could see it with my own eyes.
You already knew, didn't you?
Of course we all understood.
Hmmm.
So, if you put them all together, it would be even more amazing.
Wow.
Yes, that's right.
If the three of us put it all together, it would be amazing, wouldn't it?
I was a little surprised.
It looks like we could have a menu just for your relatives.
I was so happy to be able to use so much of it.
I was happy.
The clientele seems to be changing little by little.
Ah.
In what way?
Until now, we used to get visitors who used to throw us away,
I had an image that there were a lot of people who used to wear our goods somewhere,
I have an image that there were many people who used to wear our goods somewhere,
I thought I would drop by,
I mean, what do you call it?
Casual.
We have a lot more people who come to our shop because they are my subordinates,
Some of them seem to come here on their own time, while others seem to come here after club activities,
Some of them look like they're just visiting for fun, while others look like they're on their way home from club activities,
Some of them were young, like they came with their friends to see this girl,
There were even some junior high school students who were younger than us,
The atmosphere was changing.
You could tell that the atmosphere was changing.
It's amazing.
It's amazing that the number of new fans who come to the show is not decreasing.
Yes, it is.
It's increasing.
That's right.
We keep releasing more and more.
I think that's great.
Usually, once you get a buzz, you know you've made it big.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's amazing.
I think it was the second person who created a children's area or a family area.
I think we made a children's area or a family area for our second child.
Until now, there would never have been enough space for even one person.
The family area was not popular among children, but there were so many slackers in the family area.
It was amazing.
They were so cute.
Everyone loves little kids.
They are so cute.
Super cute.
So cute.
Mike, it's hard to hear you.
Is it coming back? I'll try to fix it.
Sometimes there are things that are being done that aren't being done.
I don't know what's going on.
Hey.
I tried again.
But I can hear it.
I can hear you.
If you take a picture from your phone...
I can hear the little guy's voice.
I can hear you.
I just fixed it a little bit. What do you think?
Can you hear me?
I can hear you.
There's nothing I can't hear.
What do you think?
I think I'll take a break.
I tried to breathe. I'm sorry. I'm always sorry.
I'm sorry.
You really need a refill.
I don't know.
My voice is OK. I'll try not to talk too much.
You haven't been here in a while, right?
Yes, it was at 3D Junior's place.
And the people who brought goods for 3D Jr,
Oh, really?
There were people who brought goods from the 3D Junior show, like huge old posters,
There were even people who were in the show.
I think it was someone I introduced my friend to,
If you referred a friend, you could get a huge poster of Oshimen.
I remember that well.
I remember that. I think it was the Lapolon tour.
Oh, yes.
I was on the Apollo tour of the Loppony Xtia Car.
The person who invites his/her friend will get the oversized poster of Oshimen.
Yeah. So not everyone is buying them or something.
So I've seen maybe one person with their own poster.
Really?
Yes, I have.Yeah.
Something about that autograph session.
I brought some people with me at that one and some others.
I've seen that before.
That's right.
We've seen it too.
One of my own.
Maybe some of the kids don't even have one.
Uh-oh.
I'm not wearing that cotton right now.
I have it, though.
I'm not bringing it.
Because the person who invited my friend, you know, if it's not that lattice, it's not in this world.
It's amazing that you have it.
It's a rare thing, isn't it?
Many people brought embarrassing photos.
At the benefit.
It's a nostalgic place, and it's also a place where people can easily come.
A nostalgic place.
Yes, it's a nostalgic place. Yes, that's right.
The people who entered from this side were very kind.
No, the hospitality was amazing.
They were kind of happy to see us and left,
He told me to come back again.
They were waiting for me.
Yes, they were waiting for me. I was so happy.
We wanted to come back too. We wanted to come again, too.
And there was some kind of café across from the stage.
There was some kind of café across from the stage,
The manager of the cafe bought some sweets for us.
He bought us sweets in exchange for a two-minute score,
And that's what happened, and I was really anxious.
I was really ready to fight again, so I was assigned to a different rank.
Yeah, that was good.
I'm glad I did.
I'm glad.
Yeah, it was good.
Well, the release event is only a few days away,
Yes.
I have a lot of events that I am going to perform at,
I'd like to make an announcement here.
I'd like to announce them here.
Let's start.
Which one do you want to start with?
Okay. Okay, starting with the yuzu?
Yes, I guess so.
Tomorrow?
Oh, well, from Lilybeth.
Will it be connected?
It'll be connected.
Lilybees.
We have two days left in the rainforest after two standing days.
First, we are going to hold a concert at the Aeon Mall on June 11.
The first one is on June 11 at Aeon Mall, Tokoname, Aichi,
Yes.
On the 11th, we will have a release on the 11th at 12:00.
And the last and final release will be held on June 24th at Raraport Toyosu.
The time has not been decided yet,
This will really be the last coffee release,
So, we are looking forward to seeing you all there.
We are aiming for a turnout of 500 people,
So we are aiming for 500 people, so we are going to have various places,
We are aiming for 500 people, so we are planning to have various events at various places, even at the Raraport Toyosu,
I hope we can mobilize 500 people at Raraport Toyosu,
I would be very happy if you could invite many of your friends.
Thank you very much.
We are the ones who are going to have this benefit event,
We have a special benefit for each event, where we give a password for each song we sing,
We have a specific meeting.
Did you come yesterday?
Yes, I did.
You did?
It was a mystery.
What's a mystery?
I don't know.
It's just...
Of youth.
Youth...
You weren't at that store, were you?
You weren't at the restaurant.
And they're all coming.
Can you tell them I didn't see it because I didn't understand it at first?
Don't be so soft, like you didn't understand.
I'd like you to tell me that you didn't see the candy shop.
I didn't see it. I didn't see it. I skipped over it.
I was skimming through it.
I didn't see it. I skipped over it and watched it.
That's what I thought.
I was sure it was going to be like that... but then he said, "Cha-cha-cha-cha.
I was like, "Oh, really?
Poor little girl.
Poor girl. Who knows what he said to her.
You never know on the first try.
huh?
That's what I'm talking about.
I said that.
Anyway...
He told me to say "I love you".He told me to say "I love you" and I did.
I said "nyan" again and that was it.
And then I said something like 3 or 4 more...
You don't understand? What's the right answer?
Someone said something to me on the way.
He told me to speak.
It sounded light, but I can't say I'm surprised at all.
What do you think the problem was?
I heard you say "meow.
Oh, they were all cats? Five or six.
Five or six of them were all cats.
So what happened to the animals?
If you tell me your favorite animal after "I love you,
I'll give you the animal ending.
What the hell is that?
I love elephants.
Wow, elephants are great.
What was that all about?
It's really unexpected.
Like everyone who's ever said that to me.
I thought I was going a little crazy.
You guys are so cute.
They tried so hard to tell me.
But it was so long.
Someone wrote it down and said it.
They said something.
And everyone's sense of rhythm was a little different.
Moe-chan's
"Cha-cha-cha-cha!
The toy chacha-chacha-cha-cha's.
They have no sense of rhythm at all.
So cute!
So, this time
What about this one?
Aitchin, right?
Let's go with aitchin.
Right?
Tenmono
Tempura.
What do you mean by "heavenly things"?
Four words like that.
I'll think of something.
Okay, yes.
What is it?
I'll decide at once.
It comes down to whether you want to make it hard, or if you can say it that hard.
Oh, let's make it really hard.
Ten-ten-ten, te-ten-ten, te-ten-ten, te-ten-ten, te-ten-ten, te-ten-ten...
Tenten-ten-ten, tet-ten-ten, tet-ten-ten, tet-ten-ten, tet-ten-ten...
It's getting a little short.
Tettenten mus musu musu musu
Tenten tten musuu musuu
tetten ten ten musuu musuu, tetten ten musuu musuu
musu musu
Oh, I knew we'd say it together
Tenten ten ten musuuuuuu
Ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten-ten...
Tenten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten
musu musu
Tenten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten ten mus mus mus
Okay.
I'll add it when I'm done.
You're right.
I don't remember anymore.
Okay.
Is that honor?
Superior?
You want to think about it for a minute?
Oh, you want to think about it first?
Yeah, just take a look at it.
You want to look at it later?
I'll look at it later.
I don't know.
What do you want me to do?
On the contrary, what do you want me to do?
Ten-ten-musmus...
Is there anything you guys would like me to do?
I don't know, maybe I don't want to take up too much time here.
I don't know, in the past, I've sung or...
Or dance a little bit.
Well, I've done that.
I like singing.
You like to sing?
I like to sing a lot.
It's fun.
It's fashionable when everyone sings.
I'll sing the same thing one more time.
I'll sing it.
Something fun for everyone.
It doesn't have to be an American song.
Steps or something.
We'll do it during the story time.
We'll have time.
If it's during the story time...
I'm okay with that.
It has to be.Or else.
I'm afraid I'm limited.
A song. Yes, please.
Let me see it.
Yes, ma'am.
That was only the first one.
Tomorrow, June 6th, I'll be performing at Shake up Arup.
For the scoring session, we're bringing back the guessing game.
That's right.
It says "reprint".
It's back?
We're going to play a game called "Ha", which is like a game called "Ha".
And we'll also have an all-you-can-take 10-second still photo session.
So please come and join us.
Please do.
Next, which one is it?
Oh, I see a shirt here.
It's an open recording event on June 10th.
I'm doing a radio show called Amegarashi no Amehera Night.
I'm doing a radio show called "Amegarashi no Amehera Night.
That's coming up.
And it's still June?
June 1, so you have until June 9 to get your ticket,
So please don't forget to get your tickets.
And June 11th, you know,
June 9th.
I don't want to push it here.
I'm going to have a release event at Tokoname,
After the release event,
I'm going to perform at the event called "Listbase 2pages 23".
Yes.
Yes, there will be various...
We will be performing on the 11th, so please come and join us.
Please come and visit us.
It is said to be one of the largest circuit festivals in Nagoya.
Please come and play.
Please come.
I will be performing in a solo event called "Acoustic Night Fantasy" on July 4.
It's an acoustic event, so I'll be playing the acoustic guitar.
I'll also be performing with idols and minions.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous, but it will be really reassuring to have everyone there,
I'm thinking of including songs I've never played before in the set list,
I've already thought of everything by myself.
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Tickets are on sale from June 3 to July 3,
They are already on sale, so we are waiting for you.
Amazing. Next.
Next. Yes, um, um... Yes,
July 15th, right? Two sparks, two sparks, three sparks, at Yamanaka Coop,
We're going to perform.
Yay!
The second round of selection will begin on Thursday, June 1 at 8:00 p.m. and end on Thursday, June 2 at 11:59 p.m. We will be accepting second round selections,
We are accepting second round selections. When does it start today? There is still time.
I'm sure some of you will forget,
Please call me as soon as possible.
And next!
We will be at a Taiwanese festival called "Manga Expo" from July 27th to July 31st.
Manga Expo, which will be held from July 27th to July 31st.
Taiwan!
Taiwan Satellite. Hello, everyone!
This is Taiwan Satellite.
What's this? This is kind of cute.
I don't know what kind of festival this is.
Since we are going to be designated for this, I hope we can all work together to make it a production again.
Please do.
That's emo, a blower dance in Taiwan.
Indeed.
And finally, we, Amehera City's one-man live, BioSci202, will be at Shinjuku Lenny on July 9.
And what a surprise, we did some soulful art here!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much.
You all said that some of you are SOULED ART.
I have a part of each.
Before.
There is no such regression us.
But, you know, the second part is that there is a little bit more left.
We are really close.
So I just read on Twitter that people were going to go to the first part and were disappointed because they didn't have tickets.
Why don't you come to the second part?
There is a second part.
There were many more.
I hope you don't have that regret again, everyone.
Because I don't know 277 people who are watching.
I think some of you are new to this.
I hope you will come and see us before you regret that you didn't get a chance to shoot something.
I hope you will come and see us before you regret that you didn't get a shot.
Thank you very much.
And now for some spacha.
I've been listening to the song from Mr. Koffi while I'm preparing in the morning to get excited.
Please keep up the good work. He said.
Thank you very much.
So, I'm sorry. It's been 28 minutes already.
It's terrible.
Why is this such a big group?
Such a group.
Okay, so this is Tokyo Izuki-chan and Mr. Setoguchi.
Please join us.
Hello.Hello.
It's me, Kofi and Hime.
May I?
What's the deal?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry to bother you.
When it comes to this place, Stachkomi's personal card comes up.
So you finally figured it out, stacomists.
It wasn't strange that it was already out there.
I guess I should turn this way a little more.
A little bit more, everybody can go ahead.
Can we pull this off?
Back.
It's okay, right?
Thank you so much for today.
Congratulations.
Is it okay if I come in here?
Yes, please.
So, this is Yuzuki's room!
Please come in!
Good evening, everyone.
I am Daikokuyanagi and Yuzuko.
It's a little confusing project with all of Daikoku, Oyanagi and Yuzuki on purpose.
My name is Daikokuyanagi Yuzuko.
Yuzuko Daikokuyanagi will ask our guests Aira, Moeka, Yuzuki-chan, and Setoguchi a lot of reckless questions,
The four of them will answer them without NG.
Of course, of course!
This is the most disgusting corner.
Are there any NG?
No, I don't.
I have a lot of NG.
Oh, really?
Not at all.
It's just like, "I've got your eyes.
Also, I drink uncle drinks.
I don't know anyone who drinks this.
Oh, I see.
When asked to buy something to drink during the show, everyone is a little down.
So you're all down.
They're all a bit down.
I'm a "echidori.
I'm from a poor family.
Then I have a question for Yuzuko Daikokuyanagi.
I can't do that.
That's okay.
Is NG big?
There are only NGs.
No, I don't.
Is that so?
Yes, it is.
So, I am going to ask you questions.
Yes, I am. Let's get started.
Tonight's guests are a group of label fans who have been talking about the topic.
And from Team President, Yutoki-chan Daikouda and Yukakichi-san. Please give them my best regards.
Please give them my best regards.
I'd like to have some.
I'm in.
Please take care of it.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Are you normal Yasuko-san, sexy Yasuko-san, cute Yasuko-san, or cool Yasuko-san?
Yes!
All of them are together.
All of them were together.
All of them, all of them.
Not a sexy backbone in sight.
Yes!
Are you Ayana's sexy Yasuko-san?
She's sexy today.
This is Yasuko-san.
Why is she different?
Yasuko-san here.
I guess she changes her style on the day.
Yes!
Ha-ha-ha.
Breath.
Breath, huh?
Exhale.
The exhale.
Thank you very much.
I wanted to thank you very much for what you did.
It's like this, more and more.
There are some side beauties.
Yabba!
That means we can make moves on our own, too!
That's right.
No, I'm an applicant.
Who are you talking to?
Such a weak boy!
I'm scared.
I'm scared
I'm being bullied
I'm scared.I'm a little scared.
At school, it always seems like Yuko is the lowest rank.
That's not true.
Hurry up!
You didn't touch her.
These two are dangerous.
They're bad.
What was that crap about you snapping?
I saw it.
I've been feeling a lot less stressed lately.
You're listening to the script with ease.
Do you do that every time?
You've been talking a little too much candy lately.
Oh, yeah.
What's the point?
What are you practicing for?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting, but we have an applicant to host.
Please.
Keep me waiting.
I'm scared.
What's the story?
Let's start with a few things.
First of all, I'd like to introduce you to Daikoku, the man you've all been waiting for.
I'm scared.
Mr. Daikoku, when I saw your outfit today, I was thinking...
Actually, I think it would have been better if you hadn't worn the purple color.
I see.
I wanted to be a different color. I was pink today.
Don't you have any memories of that?
I like Reiri Takagi.
I like Reiri Takagi, and for that reason alone, I thought purple was a good choice.
If Rini had been a different color, I would have preferred pink.
Really? Is that so?
But I wanted Reni-chan to be the same color as my guess, so I was really happy with purple in the end.
But if I had taken that away...
The color I wore was pink.
Wow!
So, if you had dressed the character in pink, would you have changed?
It might have been, right?
Hey.
No, I'm not a member.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
A little bit,
I don't know if you said "a little bit," but...
I didn't know that.
That's why I like the color pink, and I think pink is cute in costumes, too, don't you?
Yeah, yeah.
I wanted to wear pink, but now I'm already in purple.
Are you dissatisfied now?
No, I don't have any complaints.
Oh, I see.
It's because you want to do it.
Yes, I do.
You don't have color, Mr. Amegarés?
Yes, in a manner of speaking.
What is your unofficial color?
Purple.
Oh, it's purple?
But the other color is yellow.
I'll match it with the new outfit.
I like the color purple.
My favorite color, then.
It's unofficial, so I could have said anything.
Oh, I see.
You're not allowed to say it.
I see.
What color are you?
I'm red,
I'm red, but my favorite color is black.
Oh, black.
It's a very colorful color, isn't it? Idols.
It's hard to see.
Red is my favorite color for eyes.
I like red for the eyes.
You like strong red.
That's right.
I like simple things like white.
I see.
I really liked the black and red outfit.
It was great.
I saw it, didn't I?
It's cool.
It looked good on me.
I'm yellow.
Oh, yellow. I know.
It's like a "Genki" sign.
I'm sorry, but aren't you the most energetic?
Ha-ha-ha.
You've got it all over you.
It's another type of yellow.
But we all decided on this color by ourselves.
Hmmm.
We decided that purple is good for me, red for Ira, and blue for Hana,
And for the flower, we decided on blue.
green, yellow, white, red, or pink.
Oh, we chose a lot.
That's why the fans liked it too.That's why some of the fans
like before the merchandise was even out yet.
I don't think
They come out with the colors we said.
Ah, yes, yes.
I've said too many things, and it's so disjointed.
Ha-ha-ha.
What's too much to say.
More colors come out than the number of people.
Ha-ha-ha.
Colors fly.
We didn't like that either.
You didn't like it?
We didn't like it.
Why so many colors?
Well, well, you're right.
You want to dye it with tones, right?
Yes, I do.
I thought, "I want to dye it with tones.
So I thought, "You're already yellow.
Yeah. But it looks good with yellow.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah. It looks good.
I'm glad.
I know, I know.
I get it.
So, what's the image?
You know the black, right?
I see.
I don't know.
I'm a jet-black dark color.
I envy you.
Oh, that's right.
That's right. I don't know, but black is great.
But, you know, the color is jet black.
Dark color.
Dark.
A little dark.
That's a very chuunibi way of putting it.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's full of it.
You say it so clearly.
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm sorry.
Well, that's outrageous.
Well then, let's see...
Yes, what is it?
I knew it. We've met,
It's been a while since we met.
It's been quite a while.
I think we have a good relationship.
No, but..,
You don't follow me on Twitter.
Oh, she doesn't know.
I don't know her.
I only know my idol.
Today I'm an idol.
Yes?
It's jet-black.
What's Jet-Blue?
Jet-Black-Blue.
I'm tempted to say it, aren't I?
Surprisingly, Yuzuki's room, which we're going to do later...
You've been on the show many times, haven't you?
You've been a guest quite often.
Yes, of course, it has something to do with it.
What is it?
I don't know,
I think it's about time for Yuzuki-chan and the others to do something about the rain forest.
I was wondering if you could make some kind of recommendation to the rain forest.
Oh, a guess?
I'm sure there is.
I'm sure there are. I think the way I look at each one of them
I think the way they look at each one of us is changing a little.
I want you to appeal to them.
That's extravagant.
It's Okaku, isn't it?
Oh, Okaku?
If you want me to make a decision, you should appeal to me.
Why are you so uptight?
That's funny.
I'll let you decide.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You're my guest today.
Can I decide? It's a positive.
Can I decide? Positive.
Yes.
Oh, Fukkyo-san said she recommends Moeka-san.
That's right.
She might recommend it herself.
Oh, is that so, too?
Yes, that's right.
Ah, surprisingly, the chat section is properly rough.
Ha-ha-ha.
Don't get carried away.
It says, "Don't forgive.
Don't forgive me, don't forgive me.
I don't know what to do.
It's better to be honest about this, even if it's just for you, Amefura.
But do you want me to push for it? For someone like me?But do you want me to push for it? For me?
No, because one person is important.
One person is important.
Ah...
Then, I'll be honest with you.
Oh, you're here.
I've never heard of you before.
I'm Moeka-san.
What? Yay! Thank you very much.
I knew it. I don't want you to do that either.
So you like it this way after all?
It's nice.
I think it'll be popular.
I think I'll be popular.
After I just heard you say "moeka",
I got sick of Kobaseitake-san.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
First of all.
I was like, "Moeka-san recommends it.
While saying that,
Then, I thought, I'll choose Moeka-san,
I wondered if I almost said it every time.
Because she told me.
That's what you originally said.
If it is different,
I can understand why it's "oshi".
I can do it while saying it.
It's not because I was told by others that it's different.
It's something to watch, you know?
It's so fragile.
Oh, it's so fragile.
It's like, you know, you have a nice sadness about you.
You have a nice sadness,
Gentle, gentle, gentle.
This may not sound like a compliment, but..,
But, uh..,
I think that's what makes you different from other Amefura
I thought it was different,
I'm interested in it.
The fragility within the strength,
It's beautiful.
The feeling of not being heard.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I like that.
I think it's really nice.
By the way,
I don't know you well enough to know what's going on.
If it's nice to meet you,
As a face fan.
Isn't that the last thing you want?
That question.
I'm an adult,
Don't you hate that question?
When we first met,
I want to know who you liked.
I'd like to see that in an adult letter.
Oh...
I'd like you to guess "Bi-ga-Chu".
But that's probably it.
What? I'm glad. I'm glad.
Is it rude to think that way?
I've never heard that before,
I haven't heard that much about Stabler's guesses.
I'm glad.
I'm going to say it today, no nags.
I like it.
The one who was surprised by the gap was Aira.
Really?
Yes, as I thought.
Before I met you, I thought you seemed to be very cool.
I thought so too.
I get that a lot.
Right?
That's what I thought.
I'm Aira.
I'm 20 years old.
Like that.
I don't really make eye contact with her, but it's like that,
But she was surprisingly friendly and chatty,
You came to the festival that Yuzuki was going to hold, right?
When our eyes met, he waved to me, which made me very happy.
Gap, such a wonderful thing.
You didn't like her buttocks?
Yes, I like buttocks.
I'm sorry, don't cut my hand off.
That's enough.
I'm not going into fan service anymore.
I don't want to stop.
Just a little bit.
Like that?
Just the neck.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know.
But I understand.
You know what I mean?
I do.
I understand.I can understand that a great deal.
I thought Ichikan-san is just as good as he is.
Are you aiming for a gap?
What? Are you aiming for a gap?
I was pretty much aiming for the gap too.
What?
When I first met you, I was in the seventh grade or something,
I was dancing in the back of Power Go at a festival,
I thought he was a really good dancer, and I really liked the way he danced,
I was paying attention,
What? I'm glad.
I liked her because I had an image of cool girls who were good dancers.
So I thought she was really cool,
She's really easy to talk to,
She's really easy to talk to.
I'm so happy.
To the ladies?
To the boss.
I'm so happy.
That's right.
Gap unrequited love.
You still have a crush on him?
No, it's a huge crush.
The material was dumped.
I'd like to know how you were rejected.
Let's see, I just said I love you, Mr. Omiya,
I'm sorry, I'm not you.
I didn't say that!
You started from the top, didn't you, Mr. Omiya?
You didn't say that!
I didn't say that!
Dancing is different.
Really?
I'm not looking back at you.
Is that true?
I didn't say that!
Well, you'd better hug me this time.
Gap!
That's terrible!
I love you.
I'm glad to see you and Erwin.
Please tell me you really love me all the time.
I really love you.
You always say it, right, during the delivery.
Hey, say it.
He says it.
It's so cool.
I'm so happy.
Okay, one more question.
Yes, please do.
Do you want to say it even louder and higher?
Yes, please.
You were Mr. Oshiba Suzuki, right?
Yes, that's right.
Oshiba Kojima-san, right?
At least, that's who I'm talking about.
That's right.
No way, someone who is not here.
Yes, yes. It can't be helped.
It can't be helped.
So, as AmeFlash, what number shall we choose within the second oracle?
Ah!
What genre is this?
I like it.
Like?
Like genre.
Wow!
Well, well, well, well... I'm not going to go back to that part at all...
But I'll do it again just to keep trying.
I'm often asked that question even though I'm going to deliver another one after this.
No, I'm just saying that the power of the distribution after this is...
No tie-breaking?
No ties?
No, there is no tie.
Because, you know, it's not like the MCs under the sun are going to rank them separately.
You said no MC, right?
Yes, yes.
No, but I like it a lot. I really like it.
I want it so much.
Well, how about now? I know, I know.
No, no, no, no. I can tell you right now.
Are you sure?
I'm sure. I can tell you, but what are you going to do now, Mr. Omura?
I'm really confused. I don't know what to do.
Do you like him? I like him. I guess.
All groups are fine? All groups are fine.
All the stabla groups? Yes.
Yes.
Oh! What?
Here we go.
How many in the stabla group? How many?
There are quite a few.
Oh, no. What if I'm wrong?
Ten, I wonder.
No, you're right. This might not go fast enough. Do something.
The average honey master will put in this, like, solo or something.
Oh, I see.
But this time, the group will be fine.
If it gets here, it's going to be a diaper.When it gets here, it's going to be a diaper.
Uh, yeah, that's right.
Okay, then, 10.
Woo, here we go.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, that's good.
I'll be honest with you.
Okay.
Ready.
First place!
Wait a minute.
You're in first place.
We're doing it.
No, I'm doing it.
You're doing it.
A little bit.
I'm doing it, but I want everyone to like me.
That's why they don't like you.
No, I'm not in love with you right now.
How are you doing, Moe?
What do you think, Moe?
What do you think?
I want to make it to the top 10.
Oh, Moe-chan.
Don't make me say that.
What?
I want to know the real number 10.
It's not a hello.
It's not a hello. No, it's not.
Wait a minute.
I was wondering about No. 4, too.
Fourth place is high.
No, much higher.
That's a realistic number.
Yeah.
Oh, really?
I'm so happy.
That's very high.
By the way, I don't hear all of them,
You can't hear only the one before us.
Just the one before us.
So you're in third place?
Third place.
That's what I'm writing about.
You can't hear it here.
No, it's very aggressive. Seriously.
I don't hear it just here.
I don't hear it here either.
What about before 5?
I think it's Kimisa again.
Kimi-sa, Kimi-sa.
Yes, really.
There's a slight difference.
This is vashion tea.
Wow! I knew it. I knew it.
Vashon tea is a localism, a bonding experience.
This one in first place.
Wow.
This one in Firefly.
No, it is.
But thank you.
My mistake. Let's put this kind of pretending in there.
There you go.
Do you have a song by Megura?
Yes, I do.
Do you have it?
That's the one.
I really want to go to the one-man show.
I really want to go.
I really do.
So, that proves that you like me a lot, right?
Well, more than I thought.
I'm just talking about my desire to go, so I guess that doesn't prove anything, does it?
I wanted to go this far.
Yeah.
Maybe we're on the same page.
Mr. Ichikawa...
You're teaching me this one-man show right now, aren't you?
He's wearing Mr. Omiya's sweater.
Gorilla Gorilla.
What are you going to do? Are you going now? This.
I want to go.
Mr. Omiya, I even saw your absent sweater.
You know, I'm wearing it with Yuhki, the producer, at the room festival,
He's wearing a shirt and a room cover, saying he'll be there tomorrow, too, on the 8th.
This can't be helped.
It's a work group.
But the time was off.
But Mr. Omiya said he would be involved in other things.
Let's go, Mr. Tachikawa.
I thought I could go to Tachikawa and then Shibuya.
I thought it would be possible.
Timing-wise, we could go.
I really want us to take a break, so please don't come.
Please leave.
I want to go.
I'm a little sorry, but you just had a confession from Mr. Omiya.
What about you, Team Shirt?
No, wait. He's running away. Say it first.No, wait. He's running away. Say it first.
I am.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I'm telling you, right?
I've never ranked anything before,
I've never ranked anything before, so I'll rank you first.
We'll argue about it.
That's right.
You decide now.
Mr. Shirt?
You're in first place.
You just came in second.
Yes, sorry about second place.
You're in first place, right, Mr. Shirt?
I want to be number one.
Wait, I'm in first place!
I'm sorry, you, little miss.
You really were 2nd place.
I'm in second place.
That means I can only go down now.
All I can do is go down.
Keep it up, keep it up.
No, hey, you can keep it, too. It's a ranking, right?
Yes, that's right.
Then, this material now, please refer to the next Izu room.
Oh, I can do it all the time, without doing it at all anymore.
Oh, Ichikara-san, you are the kind of person who chooses to work in that way, aren't you?
I understand.
After all, human beings may have tragedies.
Well, that can't be helped.
That's just the way it is. You should have done it.
I don't have time.
Time, you know, people say it's a joke.
They call it flirtatious.
What do you mean, "flirtatious"?
Flirtatious.
So, Mr. Cribbon is cheering for me.
You said it.
What's with that comment?
Thank you very much.
No way, no way, no way. Thank you for the spacha.
That means a lot of ketchaburis answered,
Thank you very much.
I even said that I was bored without NG.
I really don't know what to say, but I'll tell you the truth.
I don't mind, but wasn't it hard for you, Mr. Daikoku?
No, well, but that's what MCs do, what they say.
What he said was absolutely right.
No, but I really like everyone.
But we wrote on our homepage that Mr. Daikoku took the 4th place.
I've taken the 4th place.
Ushira, 4th place.
We have received 4th place.
But, well, thank you very much for your hard work, excerpts.
Why, why are you talking about such a hard job?
You are the third place in Daikoku-san, aren't you?
But it's good in gegehedgutsu. So, even against orcas.
Good work.
Good morning.
You'll be hated the most.
You're going to hate me the most.
This is how I see the future of the Jookie Rampion, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
Ten minutes left, city 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, and 8 have begun.
Thank you very much for allowing me, Koichi Tamura, to perform there.
It feels like the end.
That's enough, let's go past 9:00. Let's leave it unattended over there.
Unattended and live.
You can't do that, can you?
I understand.
No, I don't mind at all.
But, Ms. Todome-chan, Ms. Todome-chan, you were in the middle of something earlier.
I don't know what you were saying.
I was in the middle of saying something.
Please stop. Please don't take it back.
You were about to ask a question with no NG.
Let's end with that one.
Oh, that's right. Well, I'm sorry, but..,
Team Shashi, what is your overall rank in your staff group?
I'd like to hear about it.
I'd love to hear.
The ranking chosen by the bigwigs doesn't hurt anything.
It's no problem at all.
It's a big-name MC.
It's a favorite ranking.
Yes, yes, because it's a favorite ranking.
Then, please tell us your ranking on the egg course, Team Shashi.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes.
You asked me, didn't you?
Why do you want to extend this?
I won't.
I won't do it.
I don't think so.
Everyone is on board.That's why everyone is on board.
We've heard a lot.
Yes, I've heard a lot about it.
We're all assuming skiing.
Of course, of course.
We are all friends.
Yes, we are.
I'll say it.
Yes.
It's 5.
Oh.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hey, oh.
Yes.
Five.
No, the first place is Ameflasi.
Our own.
That's important, important, important.
I saw that.
I'm glad.
It's the same.
Yes, it's the same.
That's good.
Okay, so we'll use the dots and go up one.
Okay, one up.
Okay, pounding.
Ok.
In Doxin's case,
Oh, my God,
Ichiban san no osama wo.
That's right.
But you know what? I don't want to do this corner again.
And, no, I'm still a senior, but it's too hard on the juniors.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
I'm afraid of anger.
Because if this was one, I would have seen the outrageous face of the complainer.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes.
No, but I like it.
Yes, yes. Because I like it. The rankings are totally different.
Yes, yes.
But when I do, I'll do it.
But I'm glad you like it so much.
I'm glad.
I love it.
I listen to it all the time.
Well, I'm glad.
Me too.
I used to do a lot of copying and stuff.
You talk so much with your followers.
No, really.
You're so kind. You're so kind.
The most troubling thing here is that Moeimi doesn't follow up at all.
No, she only does that.
That kind of thing is great.
I told you, so suddenly, with someone, I'll be imposing.
I'll do it in a roundabout way.
That, I think it's good to see Japan.
No, but I understand.
You understand.
The balance is really good. The American flag.
It's really good. It's really fun.
I'm totally enjoying this one.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
If I had said it, it would have been an excuse.
Well, next time you have a chance, I'll have a word with these two, right?
No, I don't think so.
I'd like to ask Kojima, too.
I'd like to ask Kojima to let me know what he thinks about it.
There may be a possibility.
There might be a possibility.
What are you fighting against, Mr. Michitama?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Lin Michitama.
Yes, yes.
No, it was fun.
It's interesting.
Interesting.
Until the very last minute.
Totally.
Hot! Here.
No, it's hot.
Hot.
Hot, hot.
Oh, that's interesting.
Excuse me, sir, we have to go until five minutes ago. Are you sure you're okay?
No, I'm always five minutes early because I'm not doing anything.
I'm not sitting down.
In the console room.
What?
We're not even sitting together. Neither are we.
Are you okay?
No, we're not. You're lying.
No, we're not.
Are you sure?
Yes, yes.
That's amazing.
So I can do it 200 times.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's amazing.That's great.
But, Abe-chan, this is amazing, isn't it? You do this on a regular basis, don't you?
Yes, I do. He makes me do it.
I make him do it.
That's great. You've been doing it for a long time.
It's amazing to keep going, isn't it?
It's fun.
No, it's fun.
Thanks to Shin-chan.
I'm not getting any praise.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's not a compliment.
No, really, really.
I'm glad.
I can still talk.
Yes. No, I'm looking forward to it.
We can talk about it in the room and stuff.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Let's do it.
It was fun. It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Please take care of it.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
I'll see you later.
I think it's better if I wear this T-shirt to this re-league...
Oh, sorry.
Did you make sure it's a beki... Properly.
No, no, no, I'm glad.
Oh, really?
I got a comment saying that you made me a fan of various things.
I just said to all of them, "Oh, Seventy-three.
It's only Seventy-three T-shirts.
It's OK.
It's fine.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll see you later.
I'll see you later.
Yes.
Please do.
Thank you very much.
Enjoy your stay.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
Sorry about that.
Bye-bye.
See you back there.
Thank you very much.
Could you hear me for the last four minutes?
Hey.
That's great.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
Let's go.
So, I know I shouldn't be doing this question anymore, but...
I'm going to go write it myself.
I'm just worried about getting flamed on Twitter.
I can't really see the camera.
Is it like that down there?
No, I thought about it.
Shia Chi's?
I'll tell him... he's on fire.
I'll check it out.
I can tell him to be careful.
Then we're the same. Can you say it?
I can't tell the bottom, but I can tell the top.
I'll go get it then.
Yes, sir.
That's all I have to say.
That's all for now, this is Janai4's Yujiki's room!
[Applause]
Lastly, this corner!
Ladies and gentlemen, this week's Kemin!
In this corner, I would like to show you cute videos and photos of my dog, Kemin.
Well, I thought there might be a demand for it.
Yes, Sui-kun is really expressionless, nothing changes, and his weight is always the same, so it is easy to understand his growth process.
This time, we are going to show you the bath!
Something is flowing.
Something is flowing!
Kemin in the bathtub.
Kemin's mother is grooming him.
She's getting her hair brushed.
What kind of face is that?
After this, I'm going to ask him to put on gloves again,
But if his mother's face is in it, I'll have to cut it off.
It's like this.
This face! What kind of face?
What is it? Like...
What are you filming? You look like you're about to do it.
He's so cute!
Scary!
I think we're both on the same side, Sweets.
Oh, but one more time. One more time.
Okay, that's enough.
I feel like I'm drinking the waterworks in my sleep.I feel like I drink the water supply in my sleep.
Something like this has been going on since I was a tiny little thing.
It's going to start in a minute.
I don't sleep.
Drinking water while sleeping
That's all for this week's KB-nan
Well, Yuzuki's room is going to start in a minute...
So it's time to say goodbye to Yuzuki's Room this week!
I'm sure the time will end properly since I'll be the MC.
I'm looking forward to seeing who's going to be the MC next week.
Don't worry!
After this, we will continue to Yuzuki's room.
Yuzuki's room
Yes, so we'll go to the back side of Yuzuki's room.
Wow! Surprise! Surprise!
I have an amount of time, can you please stop?
Twenty seconds left.
Yes, I mean it.
Please stop, please stop.
Please don't push the time like this.
I'm just saying.
I hope you can continue to see a lot of it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's all finish up together.
Amayadare Dare Chu for America
Se de
Seino
Amayadare chew for America shabble
America shove it
Bye-bye!
And now, before I slow down...